The Wonderful Spring of Mickey Mouse is a animation, comedy,
adventure film directed by William Reiss.
Mickey Mouse and his friends explore the promise of the spring
season through the lens of a unique nature documentary.
Mickey Mouse / Additional Voices(voice), played by Chris Diamantopoulos.
Minnie Mouse / Additional Voices (voice), played by Kaitlyn Robrock.
Goofy / Additional Voices (voice), played by Bill Farmer.
Donald Duck (voice), played by Tony Anselmo.
Daisy Duck / Additional Voices (voice), played by Tress MacNeille.
Narrator (voice), played by Keith David.
The Wonderful World of Mickey Mouse is an American animated television
series produced by Disney Television Animation for Disney+.
The series is a continuation and revival of the Emmy Award-winning 2013 Mickey Mouse shorts, uses the same style, and has many of the same
cast and crew, with the exception of the late Russi Taylor, who was replaced by Kaitlyn Robrock in the role of Minnie Mouse.
The series premiered on November 18, 2020 to
coincide with Mickey's 92nd birthday.
The animation is provided by Mercury Filmworks.
From November 18 to December 18, 2020, Disney+ premiered two shorts a week.
An additional ten shorts premiered from July 28 up until August 25, 2021.
The series was renewed in November 2021 for a second season consisting of four 22-minute specials centered around the
seasons: the first of which, The Wonderful Winter of Mickey Mouse, premiered on February 18, 2022.
The second special, The Wonderful Spring of Mickey
Mouse, was released on March 25, 2022.
The third special, The Wonderful Summer of Mickey
Mouse, was released on July 8, 2022.
The fourth and final special of the season, The Wonderful Autumn of
Mickey Mouse, was released on November 18, 2022.
On July 28, 2023, a short titled Steamboat Silly was released.
It served as the series finale.
The Wonderful World of Mickey Mouse received
generally positive reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted.